studentmoneysaver.co.uk 2018-12-16

# Privacy Policy | Student Money Saver

Student Money Saver Ltd is committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors and users of <https://www.studentmoneysaver.co.uk/>. We are what’s known as the "Controller" of the personal data you provide to us. We only collect basic personal data about you which does not include any special types of information or location based information. This does however include name, address, email, phone number. 

Please read the following privacy policy to fully understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us. 

### Your details and third parties

Your details matter to us tremendously and we promise to take good care of them.

When you sign up to our site, we collect your first name, surname, email address, date of birth, gender and details of your education. All of this information is stored in our secure database. 

We don't and won't sell your details to third parties or our partners. This means third parties will not be able to approach you directly – everything will come through us. 

It is possible in the future we may sell details of our demographic to companies. For instance, we might tell a Third Party that 30% of males aged 18-21 who signed up to our website looked at our comparison of broadband providers (this statistic is for illustrative purposes only). However, we would never include specifics about that 30%. We may sell data but we wouldn't sell details: your privacy matters and we respect that. 

### Why do we collect your data?

We've got nothing to hide. We want to send out a newsletter which includes our latest deals, discounts and articles, and so we collect your details in order to personalise and send this to the correct place. 

Some of our deals and offers require you to 'sign up' to Student Money Saver. This is because we occasionally enter into business contracts with companies, where we promise their offer will be redeemed by verified students only. In order for us to hold up our end of the deal, we have to ask visitors to sign up and verify their student status. 

### What we do with your data

All the personal data we process is processed by our staff in the UK however for the purposes of IT hosting and maintenance this information is located on servers within the European Union. No 3rd parties have access to your personal data unless the law allows them to do so. We have a Data Protection regime in place to oversee the effective and secure processing of your personal data. More information on this framework can be found on our website. 

### How long we keep your data

We are required under UK tax law to keep your basic personal data (name, address, contact details) for a minimum of 6 years after which time it will be destroyed. Your information we use for marketing purposes will be kept with us until you notify us that you no longer wish to receive this information. 

### What we would also like to do with your data

We would however like to use your name and email address to inform you of our future offers and similar products. This information is not shared with third parties and you can unsubscribe at any time by emailing [info@studentmoneysaver.co.uk](mailto:info@studentmoneysaver.co.uk). 

### Cookies & IP Addresses

The term 'cookie' refers to a small text file which, if you permit it, is stored on your hard drive. A cookie tracks which pages you visit on Student Money Saver and helps see what's popular and what you like. That way we can improve our content where it matters most. Additionally, the cookies on our site are functional and 'remember' your name for forms, until you clear history and delete cookies. 

Advertisers on our site also have their own cookies which mean they can target you more appropriately, according to your likes and interests. 

You can disable cookies on the site, though they do help the site be more functional. 

You can find out more about cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

Your IP address is also automatically logged when you enter our website and we keep a record to keep our site and other users safe. 

### Third party advertisements

You will find adverts on our pages and throughout our website. However, we're not stupid with our adverts; you won't find an advert for a pension scheme anywhere. We try and only show adverts that we think will appeal to visitors of any particular page. 

We cannot be held responsible for the content of the adverts. Hosting them does not automatically indicate our endorsement of the product. 

### What are your rights

If at any point you believe the information we process on you is incorrect you can request to see this information and have it corrected or deleted. If you wish to raise a complaint on how we have handled your personal data, you can contact us to have the matter investigated: [info@studentmoneysaver.co.uk](mailto:info@studentmoneysaver.co.uk). 

If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are not processing your personal data in accordance with the law you can complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office <https://ico.org.uk/>. 

### Updates to our privacy policy

We may, from time to time, update our Privacy Policy and our terms and conditions. Please keep an eye on this page to ensure you're happy with any changes that occur. We will do our best to keep you informed of what's happening. 

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about our site or this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at info@studentmoneysaver.co.uk, by telephone on 020 71 83 46 71, or by post at 9-10 Charterhouse Buildings, EC1M 7AN. Please ensure that your query is clear, particularly if it is a request for information about the data we hold about you. 

© Student Money Saver Ltd 2018. All rights reserved.
